dailylit.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy

We take the privacy of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for DailyLit services. Please read this policy carefully.

### YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS

In order to send you books by email, we need your e-mail address. We may occasionally send you e-mails that are not part of a book - for instance, to notify you of changes to DailyLit or to suggest other books you might enjoy.

DailyLit does not collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you believe that a child has provided DailyLit with personally identifiable information without the consent of his or her parent or guardian, please contact us at support@dailylit.com. If DailyLit becomes aware that a child under age 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information.

DailyLit will never sell, rent, or share your e-mail address with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

We currently process the sending of DailyLit emails through a third party e-mail provider (SendGrid). We need to share your e-mail address with this third party provider in order to get your email subscriptions to you, but we will share this information exclusively for the purpose of delivering our e-mail.

We may also disclose your e-mail address as required by law.

You can remove your email address from DailyLit by deleting your account. To delete your account, simply go to your profile and click on "Settings." From there, click on "Account Settings," then click on the "Delete Your Account" link.

### BILLING INFORMATION

Subscriptions to certain copyrighted books on DailyLit require payment via credit card. In order to process the payment we need billing information, including your name, credit card number, and credit card expiration date. We may also ask for your address and your card security code. We currently use a third party (Stripe) to process and store this information. We need to share your billing information with this third party provider in order to process and store your billing information, but we will share this information exclusively for this purpose.

DailyLit will never sell or rent your billing information to third parties. We will not share your billing information with third parties other than for purposes of processing the card transaction.

We may disclose your billing information as required by law.

### USAGE INFORMATION AND OPTIONAL PERSONAL INFORMATION

DailyLit keeps track of your subscriptions, including which books you are reading and how far along you are with these. We also ask you for your location, so that we can appropriately set the timezone associated with your subscriptions.

Any other information we ask for is entirely optional. We ask for your name so that a name will show up along with any comments or reviews you leave, or any posts you make in the forums. You may choose not to disclose your name or otherwise provide a username. We also ask you for optional personal information, such as your birthdate, your interests, and your gender. We may use this information to improve DailyLit, customize your experience, show you more relevant ads, suggest books to read, etc. 

DailyLit will never sell, rent or share your usage and personal information, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission.

We may also share this information in anonymous, aggregate form. Anonymous means without your e-mail address or any other information that personally identifies you. Aggregate means added, averaged or otherwise combined across a number of users so as to prevent identification of individual users.

We may also disclose this information as required by law.

### REVIEW AND ACCESS

Upon your request, we will provide you with a representation of the information we have currently stored about you. You will have an opportunity to correct or delete this information within the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### COOKIES

Like most sites, DailyLit makes use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to better customize our site and to store preference information. DailyLit will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As part of the service, DailyLit may create links allowing you to access third party sites. DailyLit is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

DailyLit may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any material changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to your email address and/or temporarily place a prominent notice on our website.
